嘿
hey
[音乐]
[Music]
嘿
hey
[音乐]
[Music]
啊
ah
[音乐]
[Music]
啊
ah
[音乐]
[Music]
我
me
[音乐]
[Music]
嘿
hey
[音乐]
[Music]
早上好，人类，
well good morning humanity
今天是 2022 年 6 月 6 日，这是他一周中最喜欢的
it is june 6 2022 and his favorite time
时间，因为周一是
of the week because it's mondays with
贝弗·范·保罗和
bev van paul and
大家好 我叫保罗，你好，早上好，
hi everybody my name is paul hello good
我是贝弗，嘿，宝贝，我
morning this is bev hey babe i'm trying
想把这些耳朵的东西放在这里，所以
to get these ear things in here so i
我看起来不像蝴蝶之类的
don't look like i'm a butterfly or
东西，不管怎样，你们都觉得
something anyway you all figured
看着我
look at me
好吧，嘿，我们有 一个
all right hey everybody we have an
很棒的节目
awesome show
很棒是的因为我们正在
awesome yes because we are dealing with
处理国家地理封面
the national geographic cover
叫做触摸的力量
called the power of touch
哦我的上帝我知道哦我的上帝我们
oh my god i know oh my god where do we
甚至从哪里开始
even start
oh
哦我们从那一点开始我不
well we start with that little i don't
知道你是否可以在那里看到它 它说
know if you can see it there it says
研究重复揭示
research repeat reveals
了我们与他人的联系如何使我们保持
how our connections with others keep us
健康
healthy
并且一页又一页地
and there's pages upon pages upon pages
讲述了触摸对健康
about how important touch is to health
和人性的重要性人类你不喜欢
and humanity humanity don't you love
that
我们多年来一直在谈论的东西
what have we been talking about for
与人类联系在一起
years continuously is connected
哦我的 天哪，所以我们
humanity oh my gosh so we wanted to
想 分享这篇文章
share this article
，首先是
and first of all those few key words
那些非常重要的关键词，
there that are really important uh
因为我们有
because we have research from dr
史蒂文森博士和加里施瓦茨博士的研究，他们说
stevenson and dr gary schwartz that say
的是同样的事情，是的，
the same thing same thing yes
所以这种接触是多么重要，
so how important this touch is
让我们从你所知道的开始
let's start with that you know as they
稍后我们将讨论
go on to later we'll talk about that it
他们如何为假肢创造触觉之类
goes into how they're creating touch for
的东西，这
prosthetics and things like that that's
太棒了，因为
amazing because touch is important from
从你出生的那一刻起，触觉就很重要，
the time you're born
他们说袋鼠触觉，他们说，呃，
they say kangaroo touch they say uh the
谁在非洲发现了 袋鼠式护理
who in africa found that kangaroo care
is even more effective when it's nearly
在出生后几乎连续进行时会更有效
continuous and starts after birth that
他们在这篇文章中说触摸是
they say in this article that touch is
我们进入这个时的第一感觉
the first sense when we come into this
是的 绝对正确 我的意思
yes absolutely right i mean
think about it
是在你出生的那一刻考虑 被
the moment you're born yes you're being
抱着
held
和触摸 肯尼斯史蒂文森博士告诉我们
and touch dr kenneth stevenson told us
它发生的重要性是
is the important it happens is the last
我们死后的最后感觉她
sense we have when we die she worked
与死亡和垂死的病人一起工作
with death and dying patients
所以
so
从出生到死亡在
how important from birth to death at
他们所谓的 k 是多么重要 angaroo touch 所以让我们分享一下肯尼斯·史蒂文森
what they call kangaroo touch so let's
博士如何
share how can a dr kenneth stevenson
证明我知道
show that i know
，
and
我们不得不说这是一位完全
we got to say this was a totally
接受过对抗疗法训练的
allopathically trained
博士医生，正在为
phd doctor in doing research for
制药公司做研究我的意思是她
pharmaceutical companies i mean she knew
对补充或
nothing about complementary or
替代一无所知，这就是她发现的
alternative and this is what she found
是的 除了博士，她还有一位医学
yeah beyond phd she had an md medical
博士，一位医学博士，我的意思是
doctor a medical doctor i mean which
他们认为这比博士更高，
they believe is higher than phd but
但当然
of course
可以，所以生物技术所以如果你注意到
okay so so biotech so if you notice the
那里的黄色，那么 biotouch 与
yellow there so biotouch is related with
所有事情有关，比如定心、
all the things as far as centering or
冥想或阅读 或平静的
meditation or reading or unruffling a
皮肤接触 始终使用
skin-to-skin contact always with
biotouch，始终使用袋鼠式触摸
biotouch and always with kangaroo touch
没有等级
no levels no hierarchy there's none of
没有等级 袋鼠式触摸与母亲
that with kangaroo touch with a mother
触摸
touching a child
孩子没有任何关系
and there's none with
，而 biotouch 则没有，她将它
with biotouch and she related it to some
与其他一些技术联系起来 在那里
of the other techniques out there that
她研究了在线灵气治疗
she researched online reiki therapeutic
触摸并不是所有这些
touch not that nothing that all these
东西都有效但是触摸的重要性
things are effective but the importance
是我们所不知道的 试着在
of touch is what we're trying to show
这里展示，而不是离开身体，就对
here right and not off the body right
对对哦，当你
right right oh that that can when you
想到袋鼠触摸
think about the the kangaroo touch
时，如果你的
what happens if if your child
孩子伤害了皮毛，他们甚至都没有想到会发生
is hurting the fur they don't even think
什么，
about it
这是我们与生俱来的，养育 我
it's so innate in us that nurturing i
不在乎你是男是女
don't care if you are male or female
，我们所有人都有
it's all within all of us that ability
能力关心同情心，只想
to care for for compassion and to just
want to
帮助一些事情妈妈立即抱起那个
help some something mother picks up that
婴儿，开始安抚它
baby instantly and starts to soothe it
并正确地抱住它所以是的 它已经存在于
and holds it right so yeah it's it's in
我们所有人之中 这就是我们是谁
all of us already it's who we are
这就是 biotouch 的美妙之处
which is the beauty of biotouch biotouch
meets us with who we are in the present
moment you don't have to go get it you
don't have to develop it right you don't
接受它
have to be initiated into it the fact
你出生的事实
that you were born
你是这个星球的公民 是的
you're a citizen of the planet yes
，你可以帮助人类治愈，如果
and you can help humanity heal and if
这个星球上有一个
there's ever a time on the planet when
需要
it's needed
它的时间，现在就是
it's now
现在
now
，biotouch 已经为这个做好了准备
and biotouch is all set up for this well
让我分享更多关于这项
and let me share a little more about the
研究的信息 加里在这里发现我们总是
research that gary found here we always
谈论
talk about
他的派对谈论爱情，但他
his the party talks about love but he
说，呃，
said uh that
他
that the data he did this
和一群新生
research with a bunch of freshman
心理学学生一起做这项研究的数据，他说数据
psychology students and he said the data
清楚地表明，虽然
clearly showed that whereas
没有联系
non-contact
我们，
us
但他做了治疗工作
he did healing work with people
非接触的人的影响很小 布
non-contact had a minimal effect cloth
接触你穿过衣服触摸的地方
contact where you touched through the
有中等影响
clothing had a moderate effect it was
直接皮肤接触
direct skin contact that showed the
在减少手术后报告的疼痛方面显示出最大的效果
greatest effect in terms of reducing
reported pain
following a procedure
哇，这些差异在统计上非常
wow these differences were highly
显着，一句话
statistically significant in a word
直接 身体接触很
direct physical touch
重要，
matter
所以他问的问题是，
so the question he asks is why
为什么主要物理的原因是
well is the reason primary phys
生理的还是心理的，
physiological or is it psychological or
或者可能是
is it possibly electromagnetic effects
与直接身体接触或操作相关的电磁效应
associated with direct physical contact
or operating
，以及他的假设和他实际上
and what his hypothesis and he actually
进入它的莫琳称之为治疗
goes into it maureen called the healing
实验呃 他的假设是这
experiments uh his hypothesis is that
三者可能都参与
all three are probably involved in the
了 biotouch physiolo 的过程 物理
process of biotouch physiological
心理学 嗯，我们说这是一个
psychological well we say it's a
整体技术，是的，以上都是，
holistic technique right yes all of the
above
但他说第二课
but he said the second lesson is
更深入，坦率地说更
somewhat deeper and frankly more
鼓舞人心 biotouch 培养的那种爱
inspiring the kind of love that biotouch
是一种高水平的爱，
fosters is a high level of love
包括移情同情关怀
including empathy compassion caring
温柔保护安全温暖
gentleness protection safety warmth
感恩 当你
gratitude and appreciation as you
探索黛博拉亲切而感激的
explore deborah's gracious and grateful
书时，我希望你能
book my wish is that you become filled
像我一样充满奇迹和承诺
as i did with the wonder and promise
，biotouch 为我们所有人，我们所爱
that biotouch offers all of us our loved
的人，更伟大的人类和自然
ones the greater humanity and nature
本身，
itself wow
哦，我的天哪
oh my gosh
，它在这里它是
there it is here it is
现在它在国家地理上是
now it's on national geographic yes
的，但我们一直在
but here's the thing that we've been
说
saying
你不必去寻找它，因为
you don't have to go find it because
我们已经在这里，
we've been here
你在 30 多年前建立了这个，
you established this 30-something years
我们有这个伟大的基础，
ago we have this great foundation that's
为每个尝试的人提供这个
holding this for everybody
告诉你
trying to get the word out for you
，已经有适合你的东西了，
that there's something for you already
这种照顾和
this this ability to take care of and to
帮助你生活中每个人的
help someone everybody in your life we
能力 你有它 它已经回来了 是
already have it it's already back yes
的，它现在回来了，因为正如
and and it came back now because as you
你所说，这是人类历史上一个非常关键的
were saying this is a very pivotal
关键点，
critical point in the history of
以及
humanity and
this
我们和
new newness that's uh upon us and our in
我们的思想以及我们改变我们的方式
our thinking and our changing the way
的这种新事物 现在生活并思考
that we're living and thinking about how
我们想要如何生活
we want to live now
biotouch 是奥布里它很干净
biotouch is aubrey it's clean
很明显
it's clear
它
it's
适合我们所有人 我不知道还能怎么
for all of us i don't know how else to
说
say it
anymore help me here
help us people
really
拿
the and the way to help is you take
那两个手指，然后伸出手，
those two fingers and you reach out and
轻轻地在皮肤上触摸某人，
you touch someone very lightly on the
在皮肤上，你知道
skin on the skin you know that that's
那是多么简单，你知道我
how simple it is you know i'm doing a
podcast with uh
jane hogan health uh
将在几周内与呃简霍根健康一起做一个播客，接下来会发生什么
in a couple of weeks and what's going to
最棒的是，我将
be great about that is i'm going to be
能够教人们通过电波伸出手去
able to teach people to reach out and
触摸，
touch right over the airwaves
就这么简单，你以前做过，
it's that simple you've done that before
是的，很简单，你知道我被
yes yeah and it's so simple you know i'm
提醒了，记住，我不知道 不知道你
reminded remember uh i don't know if you
是否在这里我们做了这个 uh
were even here we did this uh
prese 说是在动物园，
presentation it was at the zoo and it
这就是志愿者感谢
was all it was a volunteer appreciation
日，那里有成百上千
day and there were hundreds and hundreds
的人，他们让我说话
of people there and they had me talk
，那里有成百上千的人，
and there's hundreds of people there and
每个人都在大喊大叫，我站
everybody's yacking away and i get up
起来，我说 好吧，我希望
there and i and i say all right i want
每个人都用两根手指，我希望
everybody to take two fingers and i want
你伸出手去触摸
you to reach over and touch somebody
你旁边的人，
next to you
沉默，沉默，我知道你
silence moment of silence i know you
不需要做任何事情，甚至
didn't have to do anything even people
那些正在观看它的人都说，哦，我的上帝
that were watching it said oh my god
，这太强大了 在那
that was so powerful that for that
一刻，他们伸出手，
moment that they reached over and
触摸某人的脸，
touched someone on the face on the
肩膀，手臂，有片刻
shoulder on the arm there was a moment
的沉默，这种联系是
of silence the connection had been made
通过触摸建立的，
through touch
你知道，你知道有趣
you know you know what's interesting
的是，
about that is that touch what happens
当我们触摸它时，会发生什么 几乎就像
when we touch it's almost like the body
身体吸了一口气说，哦，
takes a breath and says oh
这就是
this is life
生活 biotouch 是关于
biotouch is about this rhythm of life
贯穿我们所有人的这种生活节奏，当
that is runs through all of us and when
我们练习 biotouch 时，我们
we practice biotouch we are
就像连接到所有人的本质
like connecting to that essence of all
正如加里所说的那样，
of life as gary says
大自然的生活我们是这个星球上大自然的一部分
nature we are part of nature on this
planet
我们可以理解来吧
we can understand that come on
让我们与大自然融为一体
let's let's be one with nature
你知道我们是人类我们现在可以
you know we are human beings we can now
be in the presence with another human
通过触摸
through touch
这里的更多文章与另一个人在一起 非常
more of the article here which is very
有趣所以他们花了很多
interesting so they spend a lot of time
时间研究触觉的力量以及
going into the power of touch and what
它在大脑和连接中的作用
it does in the brain and the connections
所以他们现在创造的
so what they've created now
是他们正在创造假肢，
is they're creating prosthetics
特别是为没有
especially for people that don't have
手臂或手的
arms or hands
人和 他们正在创造一种能力
and they're creating the ability that
，你把它
in the fingertips that you put it with
放在假肢上的指尖正在创造信息，
the prosthetic is creating messages that
这些信息会传到他们发现与触摸有关的大脑部分，
go to those parts of the brain that they
found that relate to touch
okay
并且他们与
and the the discussion they have with
尝试过的人进行的讨论是他们 感觉
people who have tried it is they feel
完整
whole
他们再次感到联系
they feel connected again
是的，因为手中有这种力量
yeah because there's this power in the
，他们发现
hands that they're finding out the power
触摸手指的力量 手
of touch the fingers the hands
在大脑中创造了一些东西
creates something in the brain
，帮助我们理解我们是一部分
that helps us understand that we're part
人类的你知道我们之前已经提到过
of humanity you know we've mentioned
这个并且实际上
this before and actually
在其他节目中展示了一些图片但是
shown some pictures in other shows but
如果你会看一些古老的
if you will look at some of the ancient
图片一些古老的艺术你就会
pictures some of the older art you know
知道呃艺术家和
the the uh artists and the the
雕塑以及来自你的人
sculptures and and people from the you
知道
know
很久以前你会看到
long ago periods you will see
that
他们
they paint
画天使和伟大老师的照片
pictures of angels and great teachers
并且做得很好
and great
doing this
你知道要么伸出手要么说
you know either reaching out or saying
我在这里或者不管这一直是什么
here i am or whatever this is always
been
这是给我们的信息现在回来
this is a message for us that is back
了我想知道的时候 如果我在这里有那些
now it's time i wonder if i have that
照片，哦，我知道它很漂亮，
photos here oh i know it's beautiful
那里有真实的
well there's people there's actual
人，
people
但是是的，嗯，
but yes and um
但是是的，我们已经看到了这些照片和
but yeah some of these pictures and
雕塑中的一些，哦，
sculptures that we have seen oh
它已经存在了一段时间，
it's been around a while
所以这里有一些非常有趣的东西
so here's something very interesting
，让我很兴奋你 知道
that excites me a lot you know people
人们就像
are like
我们总是很好地回答问题我
we always get the question well i don't
这里没有任何人你知道或者我被
have anybody here you know or i'm locked
锁定我没有任何人可以交谈我
down i don't have anybody to talk to i'm
只是在做缩放你知道哦你知道的
just doing the zoom you know oh the
元宇宙 只是你知道
metaverse you know that's just you know
我不想处理它但我
i don't want to deal with it but i get
对所有这些技术感到非常兴奋
really excited about all this technology
只是因为
only because
我别无选择它就在这里我知道不我们
i got no choice it's here i know no we
最好都习惯它所以
better all get used to it and so
它可能是不同的
it might be a different generation that
一代 将成为他们生活的一部分，但我想
it'll be part of their life but i want
成为将触摸带入其中的建筑的一部分
to be part of the building of bringing
，因此如果他们
touch into that and so if they're
发现不仅假肢
finding not only that a prosthetic can
现在可以为那个人的感觉创造信息，
now create messages to that person
sensation
他们也在创造这些手套我
they're also creating these gloves i i
实际上 在广告中看到
actually saw in the commercial where
他们有这种拥抱的
they have this hug
东西，所以你和某人一起放大，
thing and so you zoom with somebody and
然后穿上这件衬衫是的，两个
you put on this shirt yes the two
兄弟，两个不同的国家
brothers two different countries
哦，天哪，这太棒了，是的
oh my gosh that is amazing yeah right
，所以如果他们在大脑
and so if they're finding in the brain
中找到触发的东西 你知道，然后
what that's triggering you know then
biotouch 将自己定位
biotouch is positioning itself to be
为这项运动的一部分哦，是的，为什么
part of this movement oh yes well why
不在这里它现在就在这里它
not it's here it's here for now it is
it's part of the unfolding of what's
是我们所谓的健康社区中即将发生
coming for us in in the community of
what we call
health
的事情的一部分，它将发挥作用 阿胡 ge part 我
and it's going to play a huge part i
毫不怀疑，因为如果国家
have no doubt because if national
地理是正确的，那么触摸的力量
geographic is right the power of touch
then
就会到来，是的，它就在这里，所以对于
it's coming yes it's here so for all of
我们所有人来说，仍然有人伸出手去
us who still have someone reach out and
触摸
touch
我们在大流行期间所说的是，如果
what we said during the pandemic is if
你没有人
you don't have someone
做 这些要点，但想想
do the points but think of somebody
有人对你这样做，我们必须保持良好的
doing it to you we've got to keep the
关系，如果这种
relationship going right and if that
关系是因为我们
relationship is because we're thousands
相距数千英里，而我们所拥有的只是
of miles away and all we have are these
这些缩放会议，但我们现在可以
these zoom meetings but we now can
创造这样一种感觉 我们会走到
create the sense that we're coming
一起
together
，很快我们就会发现它是否
and pretty soon we'll find out if it's
真的只是一个全息图如果
just really a hologram to begin with if
你相信矩阵我所
you believe in the matrix all i have to
要做的就是眨眼睛我可能会
do is blink my eyes and i could be
担心不吃药是的我的
worried not to take that pill yeah i
意思是
mean there were people on this planet
在 20 年代和 40 年代，这个星球上有些人实际上
back in the 20s and 40s who actually
可以
could
带着他们的身体并将其移动到另一个
take their body and move it to another
地方并遇到一个绝对的人 casey
place and meet somebody absolutely casey
swedenborg
所有这些都很棒
all of these amazing
所以
so
你在
you're talking about
谈论真正的骗局我们谈论
the true con we talk about the
我们之间的联系
connection between us
时空
time space
距离不能打破
distance cannot break the connection
两个人之间的联系，
between two people
所以如果你正在考虑那个人
so if you are thinking about that person
doing bio touch with you
在你的身体上与你进行生物接触，然后你这样做，
on your body and then you do it
这是真实的，
it is it's real
这是一种联系，是的，所以
it's a connection yes yeah and so if
如果我们是 然后触发
we're if we're then triggering
我们大脑中的感觉，
senses in our in our brain that
将其识别为
recognizes it as touch
触摸然后它变得容易你知道我可以
well then it becomes easy you know i can
轻松地通过这个屏幕
easily reach out through this screen
触摸触摸问候
touch that two points of the greeting
和治疗的两个点将开始发生
and healing will begin to happen and
你会感觉到我是 触摸你我的
you'll sense that i'm touching you i
意思是我们参加了所有的董事会会议我们
mean we do all of our board meetings we
开始打招呼我们做了一个
started doing the greeting we did a a
我们分手到房间我们实际上
we break up into rooms and we actually
通过屏幕互相触摸
touch one another through the screen
疯狂的屁股但
crazy ass but
它似乎有效所以我很兴奋你
it seems to work so so i'm excited you
知道我们 我们再次处于
know that we're we're sort of again in
最前沿我记得做
the cutting edge i remember doing the
第一个网站时你只有一个页面
first website when you only had a page
我们在那里我知道现在是 35
we were there i know and here it is 35
年后我们仍然
years later and we're still we have been
被一些真正的大人物告知我们 我们
told by some really big guns that we
已经引进了像你们一样的人
have brought in like guys you already
在比赛开始之前，所以 biotouch 正在
ahead of the game right so something is
发生一些事情，因为我们
going on with biotouch because it we're
是保管人，它必须保持
the custodians it has to be kept
神圣，保持完整性
sacred and the integrity held
和它的真实性，它的爱的
and the truth of it the the the love
部分必须继续，这是我们
part of it has to continue that's our
job
为你
for you
做的工作 让
for for
世界上的每个人都能够使用
everybody in the world to be able to use
它 这就是我们每周一在这里做的
it that's what we're doing here every
事情 所以再次问候
monday so again the greeting take the
用你惯用手的两个手指
two fingers of your dominant hand
好吧
all right
触摸
touch
感觉它在你自己
feel it on yourself you've got somebody
身上 你身边有更好的人 感觉
next to you that much better feel that
胸骨就在你的胸部中央
breast bone right in the center of your
chest there
跟着它向下 跟着它向下
follow it down follow it down and all of
突然掉进一些软组织
a sudden drops off into some soft tissue
有些人说它比其他人更软
some people say it's softer than others
但你知道你想要什么 是的 是的
but you know whatever you want yeah yeah
在那里保持六到八秒
hold there six to eight seconds
用同样的惯用手
take that same dominant hand
感觉你的脖子后面 把你的头
feel behind your neck lean your head
向前倾 有一根大骨头突然冒出来 走到那根骨头
forward there's a big bone that pops out
的左边一英寸到一
go to the left of that an inch to an
英寸半 再次像蝴蝶一样轻轻触摸
inch and a half and touch lightly like a
它就是那种轻
butterfly again it's that light touch
触感 身体中的 ed
that's registered in the body
那是
that's the ingredient
你开始做一些令人惊奇的事情的成分 是的
you've started something amazing yes
，这很简单
that's simple we can't remind you how
amazing this is enough time which is
what we try to do every monday i know
so
you know and so we have other ways to
你也可以上网
learn it too you can go online download
下载前 10 页，上面有
the first 10 pages which has that
greeting with it
你知道的问候语，还有一个视频有一个链接，
you know and a video has a link to it
告诉你怎么做怎么做，
showing you how to do how to do it
我们马上要上课了，下一
we have a class coming up and our next
节课是在
class is in
7 月 7 月 19 号
july july 19th
是一天的训练，我们带你
that's a one day training we take you
完成整个计划，我们
through the whole program and we
实际上练习要点，看着
actually practice the points watching
彼此做
one another doing it
，然后我们有一个 julia dara 的下一个研讨会
and then we have an our next workshop
coming up with a julia dara
，呃她要和我们谈谈
and uh she is going to talk to us about
网球肘
tennis elbow
然后我们会教你
and then we will teach you the points on
如何解决网球肘的要点 所以
how to address tennis elbow so it's all
我知道做生物接触很简单
quite simple i know to do bio touch you
know it's not this huge long drawn out
process that you have to take years to
否则你
do and you don't need anybody else you
知道一旦你触摸你 受影响的我
know once you touch you're affected i i
认为这是关于你真的
think it's about you really believing
相信你可以在你自己的内心
that you can you have it within yourself
帮助别人
to help someone else
因为我们的很多编程是
because so much of our programming is
哦我不能
oh i can't
我没有它需要我没有
i don't have what it takes i don't have
这个我没有 我没有，是的，
this i don't have i don't have yes you
你有，你有它，你一直把
do you have it and you've always had it
它放在你的内心，如果你
right there inside of you and if you
想相信它，
want to have a belief in it
那就去做吧，不要抱任何期望，
do it just do it have no expectations it
它不会杀死你 它不会让你付出
ain't gonna kill you it ain't gonna cost
任何代价 它不会伤害任何人
you anything it's not gonna hurt anybody
就在那儿 就在那儿
just see right there right there we're
we're bucking the whole system here
oh yeah but
for writing this book right i just got
contacted lady in
学习
england just read it and wants to learn
怎么做 嘿，我刚刚
how to do it hey i just did a class a
certification class uh one-on-one with
和我们最新毕业的 um
with uh our our newest graduate um
nova 一对一地参加了 A 级认证课程，然后她读了那本书，她
nova and then she she read that book she
去了，那确实是我读过的最好的书
goes that is literally the best book i
里面有一切我
have ever read it had everything in it i
哭了我笑了它给了我如此
cried i laughed and it gave me such
难以置信的希望你去生物接触
incredible hope there you go bio touch
所以我们 在这里给地球带来希望
so we're here bringing hope to the
只是伸出手去接触
planet just reach out in touch
谢谢 bab 谢谢 paul 谢谢大家
thanks bab thank you paul thank you all
如果您
check out the national geographic if you
想了解更多关于触摸的力量，请查看国家地理，
want to know more about the power of
或者如果您想了解
touch or contact us if you want to know
更多关于项目的权利，请联系我们
more about the project right the power
触摸阅读黛博拉的书吧，
of touch read deborah's book right and
嗯，我们下周一见，祝你度过
uh we'll see you all next monday well
愉快的一周
have a great week
[音乐]
[Music]
我能感觉到疼痛
i can feel the pain
和阳光或雨水，
and sunshine or rain
所以这不是
so it's not caused
由天气引起的，
by the weather
但在我之后它并没有那么痛
but it doesn't hurt that much
感受你爱的抚摸
after i feel your loving touch
，我们一起度过了一段时间
and we spent some time
together
你每天都带走我的痛苦
you take my pain away
each and every day
你是来自天堂的天使
you're an angel from heaven
在
on
你身上
your body
帮助我痊愈
helps me heal so much
，随着时间的流逝我会变得更好
and i get better as time
goes
by
[音乐]
[Music]
你带走我的痛苦